ACTWU Audio-Visual Materials 5619 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- A Class Divided Frontline, 19 (Box 12)
- Leaving Home: We Do The Work, 20 (Box 12)
- NAFTA - Environmental Impact / We Do the Work, 21 (Box 12)
- Stand Up Campaign Ads, July 1995 / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 22 (Box 12)
- Changing the Way We Work: An America Works Special / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 23 (Box 12)
- Stand Up For America's Working Families: 1995 / Labor Institute of Public Affairs, 24 (Box 12)
- It's our turn! / International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers (3/17/1994), 25 (Box 12)
- It's Your Business / Laborers' International Union of North America, 26 (Box 12)
- The Great Depression - Part V: Mean Things Happening Part VI: To Be Somebody Part VII: Arsenal of Democracy, 27 (Box 12)
- Bob Mclean Show- Dec. 10, 1979, 29 (Box 12)
  moved from box 25 to box 12 during the reorganization of the collection
- Tape Off-Air Cassette - T.C.T. Segment 2: 5-22-1980 // Crystal Lee Sutton T.C.T. Interview, 30 (Box 12)
- Crystal Lee Sutton: Women in Labor Unions segment, Feelin' Free // KYW-TV: 2/3/1980 -- Philadelphia, 31 (Box 12)
- Crystal Lee Sutton / Philadelphia: Aired 1/30/1980, 1 (Box 13)
  1.5 minutes, including "Norma Rae" film clip, LIVE on KYW-TV (Ch.3); "Eyewitness News/5:30" in "Newsmakers" segment (also promo'd 1/29 & 1/30 during regular programming, including "Today Show" 1/30); 2. filmed at 1/30/1980 press conference, included
- Crystal Lee Sutton on "Speaking Frankly" segment of "Noon Report", WCPO-TV (Ch.9) CBS; Interviewed by Hugh Dermody with audience questions, all favorable - Aired 2/13/1980 from 12:41 p.m., LIVE [recorded 4/27/1980], 2 (Box 13)
  moved from box 24 to box 13 during the reorganization of the collection
- Crystal Lee Sutton interviewed by Ted Ryan & Sue Lilly: "Daytime Dayton" -- WHIO-TV (Ch.7) CBS, taped 2/15/1980, 3 (Box 13)
- Crystal Lee Sutton/Pittsburgh -, 1980; 4 (Box 13)
  "Starting Today" - WIIC-TV - C.11 (NBC) - Taped 2/8/1980 - Aired 2/13/1980 - 6:30 7a.m.; Interviewed by Jayne Adair - Crystal had 1/2 of total show as principal guest (this show leads in the "Today Show") //// moved from box 24 to box 13 during the reorg
- Crystal Lee Sutton - AM San Francisco - 3/7/1980, 5 (Box 13)
- Morning Break - WDVM-TV Ch.9 6-10-1980, 6 (Box 13)
- AM Chicago - WLS-TV 7:- May 12th, 1980 // "Amalgamated Textiles" (Norma Rae), 7 (Box 13)
- Gallery Show - 1943 // Crystal Lee Sutton, 8 (Box 13)
- Sandy Hill with Crystal Lee Sutton / Good Morning America / WABC TV and the ABC Television Network / Thursday, April 3, 1980 at 7 am, 9 (Box 13)
- ACTWU - Speech by Gregory Stevens: 26-Aug.-1976, 10 (Box 13)
- J.P. Stevens - White Horse [MASTER] / Harold Mayer: 1/17/1978, 11 (Box 13)
- J.P. Stevens - White Horse / Harold Mayer: 1/17/1978, 12 (Box 13)
- CBS - Ch. 8: Milu Kean Cleveland, 1 (Box 14)
  moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- Crystal Lee Sutton -, 1980; 2 (Box 14)
  "Sunday Show" - Live -- 3/16/1980 -- KNBC-TV, Los Angeles; "The Steve Edwards Show" - aired Thursday, 3/13/1980 - KNXT- TV, Los Angeles (CBS) -- moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- Sharon King Show: 1/24/1980, 3 (Box 14)
  videotaped at the Boston Film/Video Foundation -- Crystal Lee Sutton/Aired Between 12:30 & 1:30 pm, Live -- 1/24/1980 // Repeated 5-6 am - 1/25/1980 -- moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- J.P. Stevens Rally: 12/08/1977 MASTER, 1980; 4 (Box 14)
- Crystal Lee Sutton on "A.M. Pittsburgh" - 2/7/1980 / Interviewed by Lynn Hines, 5 (Box 14)
- Crystal Lee Sutton Segment, 6 (Box 14)
- J.P. Stevens Rally: 12/08/1977 MASTER, 7 (Box 14)
- J.P. Stevens - 2/23/1978, 8 (Box 14)
- Sam Ervin, Jr., 9 (Box 14)
- J.P. Stevens: Portion of Skit, 10 (Box 14)
- 60 Second Spots, 1978; 11 (Box 14)
  #1,2,3 Rally -- E.G. Marshall -- 9/14/1978; "Remember Me to Herald Square"; #4 General - 50 seconds --- moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- Crystal Lee Sutton - Interview for "Arkansas USA", 1980; 12 (Box 14)
  Air date: 6/22/1980; moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- J. P Stevens Debate: 7/13/1977, 13 (Box 14)
  Reel I -- COPY -- moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- J.P. Stevens Debate: 7/13/1977, 14 (Box 14)
  Reel II --- COPY --- moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection1977
- Casper Citron - WQXR: 9/10/1979 // Pam Woywod and Carol Jolman - Amalgamated, 15 (Box 14)
- Crystal Lee Sutton in Atlanta, Ga., 1980; 16 (Box 14)
  "Open Up"/WTBS-TV (Channel 17, Cable -- Ted Turner's 'Super-station') -- taped 3/22/1980 and aired 3/23/1980 from 12:15 am to 12:40 am (top of show) to cable stations across U.S. Interviewer: Bill Tush, News Director // moved from box 26 to box 14 during
- Crystal Lee Sutton on "Pittsburgh 2Day", KDKA-TV, 1980; 17 (Box 14)
  2 segments with live audience -- aired Friday, February 8, 1980 // moved from box 26 to box 14 during the reorganization of the collection
- J.P. Stevens: 2/23/1978, 18 (Box 14)
- Friendship Bridge - WMCA (March 18, 1942) // America Unlimited WEAF (8/25/1939): Sidney Hillman, 1939-1942; 1 (Box 15)
  moved from box 27 to box 15 during the reorganization of the collection
- Labors Non-Partisan League, Salute to Labor // National Defense Advisory Committee - WABC (8/8/1940): Sidney Hillman, 2 (Box 15)
- Labor & Supreme Court (3/8/1937) // Tenth Anniversary of American Labor Party WNEW (5/4/1946): Sidney Hillman, 1937-1946; 3 (Box 15)
- WNYC - 9/21/1940 // Mayor's Conference - WNYC: 9/21/1940 -- Sidney Hillman, 4 (Box 15)
- Labor Roosevelt // Why Labor Supports President Roosevelt:- Sidney Hillman, 5 (Box 15)
- ACWA Ceremonies - Opening Pt. 1-2 :- Sidney Hillman, 6 (Box 15)
- ACWA - Opening Ceremonies Pt. 7-8 :-- Sidney Hillman Health Centre, 7 (Box 15)
- ACWA - Opening Ceremonies of Sidney Hillman Health Centre: Pt. 3-4, 8 (Box 15)
- ACWA - Opening Ceremonies of Sidney Hillman Health Centre Pt. 9-10, 9 (Box 15)
- ACW - Opening Ceremonies of the Sidney Hillman Health Centre - Pt. 11-12, 10 (Box 15)
- Image of History - 20 years of the CIO, 11 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral Service from Carnegie hall - Side 5-6, 12 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's funeral Service from Carnegie Hall - Side 7-8, 13 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral - Philip Murray and Rabbi Stephen S. Wise Singing, 14 (Box 15)
- The Inheritance - 50th Anniversary - ACWA, 15 (Box 15)
- The Inheritance, 16 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman Funeral - Opening Prayer - Eulogy (pt. 1-2):-- Jacob Potofsky, 17 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman Funeral: Opening prayer, Eulogy (pt. 1-2) -- Jacob Potofsky, 18 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral - Opening Prayer: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Jacob Potofsky (July 12, 1946), 19 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Philip Murray, 1946; 20 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Philip Murray, 1946; 21 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy - (pt.1-2) - Philip Murray (July 12, 1946), 22 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Cantor Richard Tucker; Closing Prayer - pt. 2 - Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 23 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral - Cantor Richard Tucker - Closing Prayer pt. 2: Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 24 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Cantor Richard Tucker pt. 2; Closing Prayer -- Rabbi Stephen Wise (July 26, 1946), 25 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 26 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 27 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Eulogy (pt.1-2) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise (July 12, 1946), 28 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Closing Prayer (pt.1); Eulogy (pt.3) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 29 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Closing Prayer (pt..1); Eulogy (pt.3) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise, 1946; 30 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Closing Prayer (pt.1); Eulogy (pt.3) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise (July 12, 1946), 31 (Box 15)
- Sidney Hillman's Funeral: Closing Prayer (pt.2) -- Rabbi Stephen Wise; Cantor Richard Tucker, 1946; 32 (Box 15)
- Rally for Justice. Fifth Anniversary of ACTWU victory in Roanoke Rapids, 1 (Box 16)
  moved from box 28 to box 16 during the reorganization of the collection
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally (8/26/1979); J.P. Stevens Campaign; J.P. Stevens Campaign, Interviews: Danny Blackwell; J.P. Stevens Protest, Martin Luther King, Sr., 2 (Box 16)
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally; J.P. Stevens Campaign, 3 (Box 16)
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally (8/26/1979); J.P. Stephens Campaign, 4 (Box 16)
- J.P. Stevens Campaign - Interviews: Scott Hoyman, Cecil Jones, Woman Weaver, Danny Blackwell; J.P. Stevens Campaign, 5 (Box 16)
- Roanoke Rapids, ACTWU Rally (8/26/1979); J.P. Stevens Campaign - Negotiating Committee: Initializing Contract; Interviews: James Boone, Maureen Hedgepath, Bennett Taylor, Charlotte Mosley, Scott Hoyman, 6 (Box 16)
- MacNeil-Lehrer Report, "J.P. Stevens" (1977), 7 (Box 16)
- Crystal Lee Sutton "Women in Labor Unions" - Segment "Feelin' Free": KYW-TV - Philadelphia; Crystal Lee Sutton on "Pittsburgh 2Day" - Two segments with live audience, KDKA-TV, 8 (Box 16)
- Crystal Lee Sutton on Bob McLean Show (12/19/1979); Crystal Lee Sutton on "Open Up" - Interviewed by Bill Tush; Crystal Lee Sutton T.C.T. Interview, 9 (Box 16)
- Crystal Lee Sutton Interview - St. Louis Illustrated - St. Louis, MO, CBS, KMOX-TV, 10 (Box 16)
- The Dream Continues, 11 (Box 16)
- 60 Minutes - J.P. Stevens - Testimony: Justice vs. J.P. Stevens, 12 (Box 16)
- J.P. Stevens - 60 Minutes, CBS (3/13/1977); J.P. Stevens Campaign - News Conference: Clyde Bush - Interviews: Clyde Bush, Grady Davis, Contract Signing, 13 (Box 16)
- Scott M. Hoyman, ACTWU, Hollywood, FL (6/14/1984), 14 (Box 16)
- J.P. Stevens DigiBeta Tapes. (Box 17)
  - Textile Demo Spots - 1-2-3, 1 (Box 17)
    moved from box 23 to box 17 during the reorganization of the collection
  - Unlabeled audio reel, 2 (Box 17)
  - Unlabeled audio reel, 3 (Box 17)
  - Unlabeled audio reel, 4 (Box 17)
  - Joe Glaser, 5 (Box 17)
    1.Hard times in the mill; 2.Cotton mill colic; 3.Shine on me; 4.I ain't no stranger now; 5.Humblin' Back; 6.Give me that textile workers union; 7.The Mill was made of marble; 8.Solidarity Forever ---- moved from box 23 to box 17 during the reorgani
  - Set Sleeve #2, 20 (Box 17)
    moved from box 23 to box 17 during the reorganization of the collection --- Labeling is taken from side of box
  - Display Panel, 21 (Box 17)
  - 6 & 3 inspect & file, 22 (Box 17)
  - Brief Front Panel, 23 (Box 17)
  - Set Sleeve, 24 (Box 17)
  - Second Shoulder, 25 (Box 17)
  - Boyo C Plarett, 26 (Box 17)
  - Brief Material handling, 27 (Box 17)
  - Hem Bottom, 28 (Box 17)
  - Unlabeled, 29 (Box 17)
  - Unlabeled reel, 30 (Box 17)
  - Sidney Hillman Awards; Hotel Commodore (5/2/1975), 32 (Box 17)
    Tape # of 2; Reel #266
  - Sidney Hillman Awards - Hotel Commodore (5/2/1975), 33 (Box 17)
    Tape #1 of 2; Reel #301
  - Clothes & Textile Workers of America, Board Meeting, 9:30 Wed.; Floridian Room, Americana Hotel (March 2, 1977), 34 (Box 17)
  - Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers of America - Board Meeting, 9:30 Tues (March 1, 1977) - Floridian Room, Americana Hotel, Bal Harbor, Fla., 35 (Box 17)
  - Sidney Hillman Foundation (5/8/1973) - Windsor Ballroom, Hotel Commodore, 36 (Box 17)
    Tape #2 of 2 -- Reel #7-188
  - Press Conference, Washington (August 26, 1975), 37 (Box 17)
  - ACTWU Brown Lung Victim's Vigil On the Mall - Washington, D.C. MASTER (Monday, May 4, 1981), 38 (Box 17)
    Mr. Sheinkman - Thanks Rep. Ratchford -- Comments & Intro.; Mrs. Kilpatrick, Textile Worker -- Remarks; Mr. Sheinkman -- Comments & Intro.; Elmer Chatak, Secretary-Treasurer, IUD, AFL-CIO -- Remarks; Mr. Sheinkman -- Comment -- Acknowledges pr
  - ACTWU - Brown Lung Victims' Vigil - On the Mall, Washington, D.C. (Monday, May 4, 1981), 39 (Box 17)
    MASTER -- Sen. Howard Metzenbaum (D-Ohio) -- Address; Mr. Sheinkman -- Intro; Pete Seegar - Songs; Paul Clein, Former Textile Worker -- Remarks; Mr. Sheinkman -- Comments; Rep Bruce Yento (D-Minn) -- Remarks; Stop Fur Food; Mr. Sheinkman - Intro
  - Jobs Now Rally - Industrial Union Dept. - AFL-CIO, R.F. Kennedy Stadium, Washington, DC (Saturday, April 26, 1975), 40 (Box 17)
    Jacob Clayman, IUD, AFL- CIO Opens Program; National Anthem; Monsignor George Higgins -- Invocation; Mr. Clayman - re: absence of I.W. Abel -- Introduction to Walter Burke - Sec'y.-Treas., United Steelworkers of Am.; Mr. Clayman -- Ask audience to clea
  - AFL-CIO Tenth Constitutional Convention - Americana Hotel, Bal Harbour, Florida (Friday, October 19, 1973), 41 (Box 17)
    A.M. Session, George Meany, President AFL-CIO, Miss Margarita Talavera, Farah Striker
  - Press Conference of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America on Lawsuit Against Farah Manufacturing, National Press Bldg., Washington, D.C., 1973; 42 (Box 17)
    Burt Beck (off Mike); Jacob Sheinkman, Secretary-Treasurer, ACWA; Q & A Period -- Tuesday, August 14, 1973
  - Annual Sidney Hillman Awards, 1974; 43 (Box 17)
    Luncheon - Wed. - May 1, 1974 - Hotel Commodore, Windsor Ballroom; Reel #2 of 3; U-188
  - Annual Sidney Hillman Awards, 1974; 44 (Box 17)
    Luncheon - Wed. May 1, 1974 -- Hotel Commodore, Windsor Ballroom -- Reel #1 of 2; U-189
  - Union Meeting Sessions; Textiles: AFL-CIO (1972), 45 (Box 17)
  - ACWA & Textile Workers; Speech to newly formed Union in California (c1970), 46 (Box 17)
  - Sidney Hillman Foundation - Hotel Commodore, Windsor Ballroom (5/8/1973), 47 (Box 17)
    Tape #1 of 2
- Sidney Hillman Foundation - Hotel Commodore, April 30, 1976, 1 (Box 18)
  8:30 pm-9:29 pm [poor quality]
- Golden Anniversary Banquet of the Amalgamated Bank of NY, 2 (Box 18)
  Complete Program - Chairman - J.S. Potofsky; Star Spangled Banner; Invocation - Rabbi Klein; Address - Maxwell Brandwen, Pres.; Remarks - J. Sheinkman; Address - Lane Kirkland; Musical Prog. - Judith Beegan [tape ripped]
- Golden Anniversary Banquet of the Amalgamated Bank of NY (#2), 3 (Box 18)
  Remarks - Murray Finley; Address - Dr. JT Dunlop
- Wednesday AM, 4 (Box 18)
  part 1
- Full employment Action Council (April 1, 1976), 5 (Box 18)
  Waldorf-Astoria, NYC
- Who? ACWA Speaker on statistics of unemployment, 1970; 6 (Box 18)
  Manufacturing (clothing) Sector is at 19.8% --- c1970
- Unlabeled, 7 (Box 18)
- Wednesday AM, 8 (Box 18)
  part 2
- Wednesday PM; Thursday AM, 9 (Box 18)
- Thursday AM #1, 10 (Box 18)
- Wednesday (5/31), 11 (Box 18)
- Looking at Labor - KAAY; 50,000 Watts - Little Rock, 1972; 12 (Box 18)
  Aired - 6:30 pm Sunday, September 17, 1972; Subject: Farah Boycott and Strike; Mrs. Opal Stingley, ACWA National Rep.; Bill Becker, Moderator
- Labor News Conference #49-3, 13 (Box 18)
  Subject: Achievements and Goals of the ACWA; Guest: Jacob S. Potofsky, President, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Reporters: Wilfred Rodgers, Boston Globe, Lloyd Schwartz, Washington Correspondent, Fairchild Publications; Moderator: Harry W. F
- Monday - Oct. 7 #1, 14 (Box 18)
- Tuesday AM to 3 PM, 15 (Box 18)
- Labor News Conference #33-12, 16 (Box 18)
  Guest: Sheinkman; Reporters: Finley, Schwartz
- Labor News Conference #8-13, 1973; 17 (Box 18)
  Subject: Farah Strike and Human Rights; Guest: Jacob Sheinkman, Sec'y-Treas. of the Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America; Reporters: Donald Finley, Labor Correspondent for UPI, Lloyd Schwartz, Washington Bureau Chief for the Fairchild Publications
- The People vs. Farah, 18 (Box 18)
- Tues PM - Bentsen, 19 (Box 18)
- ACWA 1972 Kennedy, 20 (Box 18)
  #2 of 2
- ACWA 1972 Kennedy, 21 (Box 18)
  #1 of 2
- Thurs. Abel, 22 (Box 18)
- Sidney Hillman, 1 (Box 19)
  Poor quality
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers, 2 (Box 19)
- ACWA - 1966 - VP Humphrey, 3 (Box 19)
  MASTER
- Lane Kirkland, 4 (Box 19)
- Monday, October 7, 5 (Box 19)
  #2
- ACWA, 1972; 6 (Box 19)
- Barth Sheenan, 7 (Box 19)
  Reel 1 of 1
- ACTWU Brown Lung Vigil (5/4/1981), 8 (Box 19)
  On the Mall-Washington, DC -- Joe Glazer & the Jones Brothers - Open Program; Randall Hathcock - Sings with Grove; Del Meleski, ACTU - Opens Program; Jacob Sheinkman, Secretary/Treasurer, ACTWU -Opens Main Program; Fr. Claude Lenehan - Invocation
- ACWA - 5/29 AM: Mr. Potofsky, 9 (Box 19)
- ACTWU Press Conference (Wed. April 29, 1981), 10 (Box 19)
  ACTWU Press Conference & Briefing; AFL-CIO Building, Washington, DC; Burt Beck, Public Relations Director, ACTWU - Remarks/Intro; TV Presentation - (Tape stopped for this); Mr. Beck-Intro; Eric Frumin, Dept. of OSHA, ACTWU-Remarks; Q&A period --
- Labor Press Conference, 1962; 11 (Box 19)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers Press Conference (Thurs. Feb. 5, 1978), 12 (Box 19)
  Burt Beck, Public Relations Director - Opens Press Conference; Introduces Jacob Sheinkman & Howard D. Samuels; Mr. Sheinkman makes statement; Q&A period with Mr. Sheinkman & Mr. Samuels --- MASTER
- ACWA (Wed. May 31, 1972), 13 (Box 19)
  Reel 2 of 2; Grand Ball Room
- Amalgamated Clothing & Textile Workers Press Conference (Thurs. Nov. 10, 1977), 14 (Box 19)
  George Meany, Pres. AFL-CIO - Remarks; Murray H. Finley, Pres. ACTWU - Remarks; Jacob Sheinkman, Sec/Treasurer, ACTWU - Remarks; Q&A Period; Sol Stetin, Senior Exec. VP, ACTWU ---- MASTER
- Labor Law - MacNeil-Lehrer NETTV :- June 9, 1978, 15 (Box 19)
  Bert Beck
- 1948 Convention - Nomination of Officers, 16 (Box 19)
  moved from 5619 F
- Murray Finley: A Man and A Union (ACTWU), 17 (Box 19)
- Joe Hueter, Sol Stetin, C. Sallee & Bruce Durton, TWUA History, '87, 1987; 18 (Box 19)
  Removed from 5619/066, box 1 and added here
- 3 Interviews with retirees at Rieve-Pollock Foundation meeting in Gaithersburg, MD (Box 173)
- Unlabeled sound recording, 1 (Box 20)
  moved from box 25 during the reorganization of the collection
- Blue Murder, 1964; 2 (Box 20)
  Walter P. Reuther, President of United Auto Workers at Amalgamated Clothing Worker of America Convention (5/12/1964) -- moved from box 25 during the reorganization of the collection
- People vs. Willie Farah, 3 (Box 20)
  Sound Track - 1/4", 15 IPS -- moved from box 25 during the reorganization of the collection
- Roanoke Rapids, Ratification meeting - (Box 21)
  - Roanoke Rapids, Ratification meeting - moved from 5981 P, found in box 13 (Box 21)
- Labor's Inheritance (Box 22)
  - Labor's Inheritance (Box 22)
- Actor, Chicago I (Box 23)
- Actor, Chicago II (Box 24)
- Actor, Chicago III (Box 25)
- Actor, Chicago IV (Box 26)
- Workers Memorial Day, [JS/Diaz/Bustos Chile], 1989 (Box 27)
- Workers Memorial Day, David Dinkins, El Salvador/Torture (Box 28)
- New York State Board/Scholarship/Dinkins/ (Box 29)
- Sheraton Center Pts 1 (Box 30)
  Originally there were pts 1-4 (pt. 4 not found) -- moved from box 19 to box 9 during reorganization of the collection
- Sheraton V220 - tape #2 (Box 31)
- Sheraton V220 - tape #3 (Box 32)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Chicago/Central States (Box 33)
- NYACTWU Interviews (Box 34)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Montreal Joint Board (Box 35)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from New England ACTWU (Box 36)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Minnesota ACTWU (Box 37)
- Loevy, Hoover and Campobasso reminiscing on Murray Finley (Box 38)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Arkansas District ACTWU (Box 39)
- Father Munoz and Consulo Perez reminiscing on Farah and Murray Finley (Box 40)
  Moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- Montreal Joint Board reminiscing on Murray Finley (Box 41)
- San Antonio District reminiscing on Murray Finley (Box 42)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Southern Textile Region, ACTWU (Box 43)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Cleveland Joint Board (Box 44)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Monsignor Higgens (Box 45)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Ceasar Chavez (Box 46)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Coretta Scott King (Box 47)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from El Paso ACTWU (Box 48)
- Farewell to Murray Finley, from Georgia Sub-Regional (Box 49)
- KSUL 90.5, 6 PM (Box 50)
- Textile Voices: Joe Glazer & his guitar (Collector Record) (Box 51)
- Amalgamated Bank (Bert Beck) (Box 52)
- Jeff Ballinger: CBSTV Editorial: 12/24/1979 (Box 53)
- Minimum Wage / ABCTV November 19, 1980 ABCTV For: Beck (No Charge) (Box 54)
- Cotton Dust: 1.CBSTV-June 20, 1978; 2.ABCTV a.m. - June 20, 1978; 3.CBSTV a.m. - June 20, 1978; 4.ABCTV 7 pm - June 20, 1978 (Box 55)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Walter F. Mondale (Box 56)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Jimmy Carter (Box 57)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Douglas Fraser (Box 58)
- Personal Tribute and reminiscences on Murray Finley by Lane Kirkland (Box 59)
- "J. P. Stevens" David Brinkley, NBCTV, 1978 (Box 60)
- "Bert Beck, Amalgamated, Picket J. P. Stevens" NBCTV (Box 61)
- J.P. Stevens Pickets: March 1, 1977; ABCTV & WPIX (Box 62)
- "J. P. Stevens Company" NBC/ABC reports, 1978 (Box 63)
- "J. P. Stevens" Black News, 1977 (Box 64)
  removed from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- Audio, NBC News, "Sweat Shops" (Box 65)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers.TV Capsules September 15, 1977 (Box 66)
  1.NBCTV 11 pm; 2.Ch.5 TV 10 pm; 3.Ch.2 YB 11 pm; 4.NBCTV 6 pm; 5.CBSTV 6 pm; 6.ABCTV 6 pm; On Cuomo Endorsement -- moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- Farewell to Murray Finley from Pacific Northwest ACTWU (Box 67)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers TV Sound Capsules: CBSTV 6pm: Metromedia TV 10pm/WPIXTV 10pn: November 11, 1974 (Box 68)
- Textile Industry-Workers Panel / McNeil-Lehrer Report NET March 12th, 1978: &:30 pm (half-hour) (Box 69)
- Amalgamated, 1977 (Box 70)
  1.CVSTV 7am - 4/14/1977; 2.NBCTV 7am - 4/14/1977; 3.NBCTV 8am - 4/14/1977; 4.ABCTV 11pm April 13, 1977; 5.CBSTV 11pm - April 13, 1977; 6.NBCTV 11pm -April 13, 1977 --- moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- American Federation of Labor and Congress of Industrial Organization - Save Social Security Spots (Box 71)
- "Joyce Miller" News audio, 1980 (Box 72)
- Southern Textile Region - Taped Reminiscences of Murray Finley by ACTWU Members & Staff (Box 73)
- 60 Minutes, "J.P. Stevens", 1977 (Box 74)
- J.P. Stevens - Amalgamated - NBCTV 6:30 PM - April 24, 1977 (Box 75)
- J.P. Stevens/Amalgamated NETTV MacNeil-Lehrer Report - December 2, 1977: Victor Riesel "CUE" Unions - Ch.5 TV 10pm 12/2/1977 (Box 76)
- J.P. Stevens - Union: NBCTV 6:30 pm (Sound) -- July 24, 1977 (Box 77)
- 1. J.P. Stevens (Riesel) Ch.5 - November 10, 1977: 2.Humphrey Hawkins JC - NBCTV 11/10/1977 (Box 78)
- McNeil Lehrer Cotton Dust Standards (Box 79)
- Amalgamated Clothing Union/J.P. Stevens - NBCTV 7 am: 3/8/1978 (Box 80)
- P.R. Bert Beck Kamber Reps. - March 9, 1982; PR Kamber Reps. - only few mins on side B2 (Box 81)
- Bishop Mergers (Box 82)
- Joyce Miller (Box 83)
- 3/1/1977 (Box 84)
- J.P. Stevens Annual Mtg. - March 1, 1977 (Box 85)
- Farah - Pittsburg - CORCORAN - 10/26/1973 (Box 86)
- Good Men & True With Love Shall Ye Build; The Man Who Sold The Brooklyn Bridge; The Man Who Dared (Box 87)
- J.P. Stevens (Box 88)
- 3/23/1980 (Box 89)
- 10/10, 10/11: M.F., MF, MF, Sols; GEB - 10/11-- two tapes (Box 90)
- SS- tape 2 (Box 91)
- Stravinsky Petroucmka-tape 1 (Box 92)
- Gloria Jacobs - KTLA air - 7/6/1979 (Box 93)
- Bill Hall (Box 94)
- NYJTB - - ACTWU Dinkins, Scholarship Parade (Box 95)
- El Salvador Jennifer Casolo (Box 96)
- Speeches - Roanoke Rapids-pt.1 (Box 97)
  4 tapes moved from box 19 to box 9 during the reorganization of the collection
- J.P. Stevens Speeches - tape 2 (Box 98)
- J.P. Stevens Speeches - tape 3 (Box 99)
- J.P. Stevens Speeches - tape 4 (Box 100)
- J.P. (labeling has rubbed off) (Box 101)
- Sheinkman (Box 102)